[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Venus maximum elongation?", "correct_answer": "47.8 Degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["48.7 Degrees", "24.5 Degrees", "177.8 Degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is entomophobia a fear of?", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["Dust", "Cows", "Birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fill in the missing word in this quote from Bee Movie.            \nWell, theres Bee Columbus, Bee Ghandi, even Bee-________.", "correct_answer": "Jesus", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Jim Carrey", "Picasso"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet in the Solar System is sometimes referred to as Earths sister planet?", "correct_answer": "Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Mars", "Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is not true about pears?", "correct_answer": "They promote allergic reactions.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "They are rich in vitamin A.", "They are rich in potassium."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Genetic tests of all known potato species show that this country was the place they originally came from.", "correct_answer": "Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Colombia", "Paraguay", "Ecuador"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Duvall stars in No Country for Old Men, which won Best Picture at the 80th annual Academy Awards,.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sleepers, Michael Sullivan took on the case for the prosecution against his friends because he wanted to get back at the guards at the Wilkinson Home for boys.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elurophobia means fear of cats.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When swimming, an elephant will use its trunk as a snorkel.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World and Rat Race, respectively?", "correct_answer": "Stanley Kramer and Jerry Zucker", "incorrect_answers": ["Federico Fellini and Tim Burton", "Robert Aldrich and Garry Marshall", "Blake Edwards and Stephen Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of Marie Curies two daughters, Irene and Eve, followed in her mothers footsteps and won the Nobel Prize in Chemistry?", "correct_answer": "Ir\u00e8ne", "incorrect_answers": ["neither of them", "Eve", "both"]}]